(ﾆｰﾅ･ﾄﾞﾗﾝｺﾞ)おはよう！
おう おはよう！
-Morning!
-Good morning!
おはよう｡
-Morning!
-Good morning!
I haven't seen you around.
Are you new to Anatae?
(絵描き)
見ない顔だけど 最近 王都に？
うん｡
(絵描き)名前は？
What's your name?
ニーナよ｡
Nina.
The days when men bow to gods
(ｼｬﾘｵｽ17世)人が神を崇める時代は
終わったのだ｡
are over.
私 こいつを捕まえてみよっかな｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)はい!?
Maybe I'll try catching this guy.
Stop!
待てぇ～～！
ドォーン！
グルルル… グオォーー！
Good morning.
(ﾘﾀ)おはよ｡
はい!?
大丈夫よ｡
Oh my God!
Don't worry.
This is my assistant, Rocky.
これは 私の助手のロッキー｡
Rocky?
ロッキー？
私は リタ｡ お医者さんよ｡
I'm Rita. Doctor Rita.
Doctor?
お医者さん？
(ﾘﾀ)そう｡➡
Yes.
Despite how I look, I'm much older than you are.
こう見えても
あなたよりも ずっと年上よ｡
Really?
ほんとに？
ほんとよ｡ ゾンビだから｡
Really. Because I'm a zombie.
(ﾘﾀ)私のことより
あなた 突然 竜に変身して➡
Enough about me.
Is it true that you transformed into a dragon
and rampaged through the city?
大暴れしたって ほんとかしら？➡
You don't remember?
覚えてないの？
あっ…｡
I guess I did it again.
私 またやっちゃったんだ…｡
(ﾘﾀ)あなたは そのあと気を失って
ここに運ばれてきたのよ｡
You blacked out after that and were brought here.
誰が運んでくれたの？
(ﾘﾀ)アザゼル｡
Who carried me here?
-Azazel.
-Who's that?
誰？ それ｡
Maybe you know him as the rag demon.
(ﾘﾀ)
包帯悪魔と言ったら分かるかしら｡
Rag demon?
包帯悪魔？ あっ そうだ！
Oh, right! I was trying to catch the rag demon!
私 包帯悪魔を
捕まえようとして…｡
(ﾘﾀ)そんなことより
あなたは 人なのかしら？
Anyway, are you even human?
What?
Or are you a dragon?
それとも 竜なのかしら？
If we had that girl's power...
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)あの娘の力があれば…｡
RAGE OF BAHAMUT
DRAGON'S VILLAGE
How are you, Mom?
(ﾆｰﾅの声)
｢お母さん お元気ですか？➡
Stop!
私は 相変わらず
神であるバッカスさんの馬車に➡
I'm still staying with the god Bacchus in his carriage.
居候させてもらっています｡➡
Stop it!
神様のおうちは住み心地がよく➡
His home is very comfortable,
and he treats me very well.
バッカスさんも 私を とても
かわいがってくれています｣｡
You're still here? You idiot!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)
まだいたのか てめぇ バカ野郎！
あぁ…｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ クワッ クワッ！
His pet bird is very cute too.
(ﾆｰﾅの声)｢ペットの鳥も
とても かわいらしいです｡➡
I've also found work.
仕事も見つかりました｡➡
It's perfect for a girl like me.
女の子の私に
ぴったりの仕事です｡➡
Everyone compliments me,
みんなが
私のことを褒めてくれるので➡
一生懸命 頑張ってます｣｡
and that makes me want to work hard.
Nina! Mind giving me a hand too?
(労働者)
ニーナ こっちも頼むぞ～！
は～い！
Okay!
(労働者たち)おおっ｡
(労働者)おい｡
(ﾆｰﾅの声)｢王都は 里と違って➡
Compared to our village,
信じられないくらい
活気があります｡➡
the capital is incredibly lively.
優しくしてくれる人たちも
いっぱいいます｣｡
There are so many kind people here.
Thanks!
ありがとう！
ドン！
My only worry is that...
(ﾆｰﾅの声)
｢でも 一つだけ不安なのは➡
...compared to our village, there are
so many young men in the capital.
里と違って 王都には➡
若い男の人たちが
いっぱいいることです｣｡
But I'm totally fine!
(ﾆｰﾅの声)
｢でも 全然 大丈夫だから➡
You don't need to worry about me.
心配しないでください｡➡
I'll send back money once I've earned enough.
まとまったお金ができたら
送ります｡➡
私は今日も元気です｣｡
I'm having a good time here.
Thwarted by the sudden appearance of a dragon,
突如 現れた竜に阻まれて➡
包帯悪魔を
取り逃がしたということか？
you let the rag demon escape?
Yes, My Lord.
I hear the dragon was quite the handful.
その竜 なかなかの
暴れっぷりだったそうではないか｡
I would have liked to have seen that.
一度 目にしたいものだな｡
失望させるなと言ったはずだが｡
I believe that I told you
not to disappoint me.
Apologies, My Lord.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)申し訳ございません｡
オルレアン騎士団の
包帯悪魔討伐の任を解く｡
I am relieving the Orleans Knights of their mission
to hunt the rag demon.
これより
当任務は 漆黒兵部隊に命ず｡
The mission will be reassigned to the Onyx Soldiers.
You are dismissed.
下がれ｡
Have Kaisar Lidfard followed.
カイザル･リドファルドを見張れ｡
(隊長)御意｡
As you command.
Captain!
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)団長
なぜ いま一度チャンスをと➡
Why did you not ask His Highness
for another chance?
陛下に申されないのですか！
昨日も 悪魔を人質とする➡
Especially after we tarnished the Orleans Knights' name
by holding demons hostage to comply with their plan.
オルレアン騎士団には
あるまじき作戦を➡
強行したというのに
ここで諦めるのですか!?
Are we just going to give up?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)我々が 幾度となく➡
It does not change the fact that we have let
the rag demon slip away on multiple occasions.
包帯悪魔を取り逃がしたことは
事実だ｡
しかし 団長！
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)アレサンド｡
But, Captain!
Alessand!
I've been waiting for you.
≫(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)待っていたぞ｡
ん？
ふん｡
Pardon me, coming through.
失礼しま～…｡
おい 待て！
うっ… ううっ！
Hey, stop right there.
Do you not remember me?
貴様 俺を覚えていないのか？
What?
俺と組め｡
はあ？
Join me.
Huh?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)俺に お前の力を貸せ｡
Join forces with me!
やめて！
貴様の力は➡
Stop it!
Your power is a threat to the humans.
人間どもにとって脅威だ｡
あなた
さっきから 何言ってるんですか？
I have no idea what you're talking about!
If you're a demon,
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
貴様も魔族の端くれなら➡
do you not resent the humans of this city as well?
この街の人間どもに
腹が立たないのか？
知りません｡
ちっ｡
I don't know what you mean!
知らぬなら教えてやる｡
I will educate you then.
ついてこい｡
Follow me.
Come on, follow me!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)ついてこい！
あっ ええっ…➡
はい｡
Okay.
The humans used to dread the demons.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)かつて 悪魔は
人間どもの恐怖の対象だった｡➡
And in order to fight their fears,
その恐怖に抗うために
ヤツらは 神を崇拝した｡
mankind turned to worshipping the gods.
あなた 人間が嫌いなんですか？
Do you hate humans?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
ああ 大嫌いだ｡ だが もはや➡
Yes, I hate them!
Demons have been made their slaves now.
悪魔は
人間の奴隷に成り下がっている｡
It's all that man's doing.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)全ては あの男だ｡
｢あの男｣？
That man?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)シャリオス１７世｡
ヤツによって 人間たちは➡
Charioce XVII.
He brought humans the power
to vanquish the demons.
悪魔を圧倒する力を手に入れた｡
5 YEARS AGO
DEMONS' CAPITAL
COCYTUS
Charioce XVII razed
the demons' capital, Cocytus,
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)俺たちの魔都 ｺｷｭｰﾄｽを
滅ぼしたシャリオス１７世は➡
大量の悪魔たちを
無理やり この王都に連れてきて➡
abducted many demons from their homes,
and enslaved them.
奴隷にしたのだ｡➡
悪魔の犠牲のうえに成り立つ
この繁栄｡➡
This prosperity built on the backs of demons
俺には我慢ならん｡
is something I cannot bear!
いけない！
Oh, no!
(子供)放せよ！
ん？
Let go of it!
(子供)俺が見つけたんだよ！
I found it!
(子供)
違う… 違うだろ｡ やめろ！➡
No!
Stop it!
放せ！ 俺の 俺の！
It's mine! It's mine!
Let go!
私の里には
こんなのなかった｡ あっ｡
This never happened in my village.
The humans stripped him of his wings
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
あいつは 人間どもに羽を刈られ➡
and crushed his windpipe.
喉を潰されている｡
えっ！
I found Mugaro being sold into slavery.
あいつは… ムガロは もともと➡
奴隷として売られていたところを
拾ったのだ｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)地に落ちた悪魔の地位を
復活させるには➡
In order to restore these fallen demons to their rightful place,
I need the power to lay waste
to the foundations of everything in existence.
何もかも 根底から
ぶち壊す力が必要なのだ｡
貴様には その力がある！
えっ？ 私 そんな力ないです｡
And you have that power!
But I don't!
うそをつくな！
俺は見た｡ 貴様が竜になり➡
Don't lie! I saw it with my own eyes!
You turned into a dragon and made those humans
cower! You are what I need!
人間どもを蹴散らす姿を見て
確信したのだ｡
やめて！ 私もう 竜になんか
なりたくない｡ 放して！
Stop it! I don't want to turn into a dragon anymore!
Let me go!
黙れ！
貴様も魔族の血を引くのなら➡
Shut up! If you have demon blood
running through your veins,
その力を俺たちのために使え！
then use your power for us!
えっ？ やだ｡
No! I don't even understand!
意味分かんない｡
分かれ！
-Make yourself understand!
-I can't!
分かんない！
自分でやればいいじゃない！
Why don't you do it on your own!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
貴様じゃなきゃダメなんだ！
It has to be you!
ドクン ドクン…(鼓動)
なんでよ！
あんた 包帯悪魔なんでしょ？
But why?
You're the rag demon, aren't you?!
うるさい｡ 俺の言うとおりに…｡
Shut up, just do as I-
バキッ！
リタ！
Rita!
あんた 包帯悪魔やめて
変態悪魔になったの？
I thought you were a rag demon, not a nag demon.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)くっ… ゾンビ女め｡
そろそろ 仕事の時間でしょ｡
Stupid little zombie girl.
Shouldn't you be going off to work soon?
早く行きなさいよ｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)ちっ｡
Hurry up and go.
俺は諦めんぞ｡ 行くぞ｡
I'm not giving up.
Let's go.
RAGE OF BAHAMUT
(悪魔)フンッ！ ンンー ンッ！
ハァ ハァ… ヤッ！
ザシュ！(斬る音)
(悪魔)ウッ！
ウオー！
グサッ！(刺す音)
(観客)何やってんだよ！
(観客)なんだよ おい！
(観客)
遊びじゃねぇんだよ バカ野郎！
(観客)バカ野郎
何やってんだよ このやろう！
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)バカ野郎 んん…｡
How are you, Mom?
(ﾆｰﾅの声)
｢お母さん お元気ですか？➡
私は今日 王都の中で➡
I saw some miserable-looking demons
in the capital today.
かわいそうな悪魔さんたちを
見ました｡➡
どうやら 王都には➡
It seems here are a lot of things in
the capital that I don't know about.
私の知らないことが
いっぱいあるみたいです｡➡
Some weird black demon...
変な黒い悪魔から
私も魔族だと言われるし｣…｡
told me I was a demon too.
((貴様も魔族の血を引くのなら➡
If you have demon blood running through
your veins, then use your power for us!
その力を俺たちのために使え！))
(ﾆｰﾅの声)｢お母さんに
誰にも教えるなと言われている➡
Just like you asked, I haven't told anyone the
secret of what makes me turn into a dragon.
竜に変身しちゃうきっかけは
ちゃんと ないしょにしています｡➡
But...
けど｣…｡
Humans and demons...
人とか悪魔とか➡
I really don't understand.
よく分かんないな｡
Oh, well!
まいっか｡ もう寝よう｡
Time for some shut-eye!
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ｡ んん… ん？
グサッ！
(貴族)ぐわっ！
グサッ グサッ！
(貴族)ぐわっ ぐわっ！
グサッ！
(貴族)うっ…｡
ドサッ(落ちる音)
≫(貴族)あっ ああっ…｡
よ… よせ！
Don't!
た… 頼む 命だけは…｡
Please!
Anything but my life!
ああっ！
あっ あっ あっ ああぁ～！
Stop!
≫(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)やめろ！
(貴族)た… 助けてくれ 頼む！
Save me, please!
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)
お前の正体は分かっている｡➡
I know who you are.
I'm not here to fight.
戦う気はない｡ 止めに来たのだ｡➡
I came to stop you.
King Charioce is serious.
シャリオス王は本気だ｡
すぐに王都を去れ！
Get out of the capital immediately!
You're worried for my life?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)俺の命の心配をするのか？
Well, look how far you've come.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)立派になったものだな｡
Will continuing to murder humans
お前が人間を殺し続ける先に➡
お前たち悪魔が望むものは
本当にあるのか？
really lead you to the future you want for demons?
グサッ
あっ ああっ あぁ…｡
あっ… 貴様！
You fiend!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)この状況を見て よく
そんな たわけたことが言える｡
You have some nerve to see this place
and still say something so stupid.
My God.
これは…｡
Tell me: between the scum I've just killed
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
俺が 今殺したゲス野郎どもと➡
ここで飼われた
無害で無力な悪魔たち➡
and these harmless, powerless demons...
殺されて当然なのは どっちだ？➡
who deserves to die?
貴様の騎士道とやらには
悪魔の命は対象外か？
Does your chivalry not count the lives of demons?
I don't know where your misunderstanding came from,
but I'm a demon, an enemy of mankind.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)何を勘違いしているか
知らないが➡
俺は悪魔だ｡ 人間どもの敵だ｡➡
I vow to make you all regret
what you've done to us demons.
貴様らが悪魔にした仕打ち
それを必ず後悔させてやる｡➡
I will kill as many people as necessary
in order to do that.
そのために 何人だって俺は殺す｡
お前は間違っている｡
You're making a mistake.
No good can come from vengeance.
復讐の先に理想はない｡
憎しみが増していくだけだ｡
It will only create more hatred!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)きれい事を言うな｡
所詮 貴様も 王の犬ではないか｡
Enough with your naive sentimentality.
You're nothing but the king's dog.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)うわっ！
ドサッ！
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ううっ…｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)貴様など➡
You're even lower than other the humans I've killed.
これまでに殺してきた人間どもの
それ以下だ｡➡
At least they were worth killing.
殺す価値すらない｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)うっ ぐわっ！
ぐぅ～… うっ ぐっ！➡
くそっ 人間どもがぁ～！
Damn you filthy humans!
It's okay, it's okay
I cast the usual spell
Stagnation, stagnation
My words and heart are at odds
Default
I've taken all the paint
And mixed up all the colors
Until you're left with me
So fragile
Yet strong
Close to overflowing
But not spilling
Because I'm incomplete
I won't amount to much
This is just a good luck charm
I'm not asking for your help
I was just clinging to you
Let's end it all today
I'm done living this pointless life
I've taken my last pointless breath
To whom it may concern, see ya and goodbye
I killed the person I was yesterday
A new morning is coming
I see.
やはり カイザルは
包帯悪魔とつながっていたか｡
So Kaisar was connected to the rag demon
as I thought.
(隊長)いかがいたしましょう？
What shall I do?
Leave him. Let's see where it leads.
よい 泳がせておけ｡
(隊長)はっ｡
Yes, My Lord.
それよりも
鎧の力を無効化する子供か…｡
More important is the child who is able
to nullify our armor...
I believe it could be the child
we lost sight of two years ago.
(隊長)おそらくは ２年前➡
我々が見失った
あの子供ではないかと｡
生きていたか｡
So he's still alive.
その子供も
包帯悪魔とともに消せ｡
Kill the child along with the rag demon.
今度こそ抜かるな｡
(隊長)はっ｡
Do not fail this time.
Yes, My Lord.
The rag demon and the holy child, is it?
包帯悪魔と
聖なる子供… か｡
面白い｡
How interesting.
-This is Nina Drango!
-This is Azazel AKA Aza-nii!
Young lady,
Songs aren't as simple as you think!
No, no.
You're nonchalant yourself!
Next time on Rage of Bahamut: Virgin Soul,
"Close Encounter."
Baha Soul!!
Baha Baha Baha Soul
You better tune in next time.